Morning Musume。' It's 14!
Morning Musume。ヌs 73rd new single will be released on October 25th .
The title of the song is "Sukkoku Fever! Bake Up Call! Mezame Toki! And Devining Shine! The single will be a triple A-side single with three songs.
Yes, "Sukkoku Fever! The first song, "SUTSUGOKU FEVER!", was a surprise to the members as well as to the male audience who laughed,
Yoshiko-sensei choreographed the chorus of the song, and it is her wish that everyone will dance to the chorus,
I hope everyone will join in and dance the choreography "Sukkousoku Fever! I would be very happy if everyone could do the choreography "SUTSUKODO FEVER!
The second song, "Bake Up Call! Mezameru toki! is a song in which the voices of the 14 members are expressed in a very unique way,
The voices of the 17th term members, who are participating in this single for the first time, are of course also very good,
It's great, isn't it?
It's great, isn't it? The single has been performed 5 or 7 times as a great individuality,
The lyrics are interesting because they are a play on words from previous singles.
I hope you will enjoy listening to it.
The third song, "Never Ending Shine!
We sang most of the songs together,
But we are all singing together, and we are all doing the same formation,
The lyrics of all the members' parts are "What is this love? I think it's very beautiful.
I think it's very beautiful,
I think the overall worldview of the song is one of deep love,
While recording the song, I was thinking about the feelings of Morning Musume。 I was able to sing the song while thinking about the feelings of the fans,
I was able to sing the song while thinking about the feelings of Morning Musume,
I would be happy if you could listen to it.
This single is my last single as I am graduating.
The fact that the debut single of the 17th term and my last single were released together gives me a great sense of certainty,
I think it will be a wonderful single that will remain in your memories for a long time to come.
Please listen to it a lot.
Please look forward to the new single!
Enjoy!
That's all for Morning Musume。 23.
Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。 13 with Rio Kitagawa,Morning Musume。' 13, and Rio Kitagawa,
I am Kaon Ishiguri from Ocha-no-Ma.
We will be presenting this time together, so please bear with us until the end.
Last month, I, Rio Kitagawa, released my fourth photo book, "Refreshing Season.
This is the fourth consecutive year that I have released a photo book,
I have always photographed the theme of summer in Okinawa, or rather, the scenery there,
But this time, they granted my wish and we were able to shoot in the snow in winter.
I had only told them that I wanted to shoot in the snow,
In fact, we were able to pack three seasons into one book: snow, spring cherry blossoms, and summer,
As you flip through the pages of the book, you can really feel the change of the seasons,
That is the main point of the book.
And Morning Musume。 13 has started their fall tour.
At the time of this recording, the tour has not started yet,
This is the first tour for the 17th term and the last tour for Ms. Fukumura,
The setlist included songs that I remember and songs that I had fond memories of,
The setlist includes some memorable songs and some nostalgic songs, and the freshness of the 17th term members and the fact that Ms. Fukumura is getting angry with the members makes this tour very attractive,
If you are in the area, please come and see us.
Please come and visit us if you are in the area.
Ochanoma will start its fall tour on October 7.
This is the first live house tour for Ochanoma,
This tour will take us to all 47 prefectures in Japan,
This will be the first time for Ochanoma to visit some of the 47 prefectures in Japan,
We hope you are looking forward to it.
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look at the video.
Music
Boom, boom, boom in the wide sky
The bus is taking us on a ride
We're flapping our wingsI'm flapping my wings
Beyond my dreams
Boom, boom, boom on a yellow sunset
I'll kiss you without a word
We'll make an everlasting vow
I love you
OK, OK, OK!
Even if it's just for a day
A confession
Or a kiss
OK!
A day is more than an adult
Gently pinky nez
Gently long lonesome
Honda
Oh Oh Oh Oh
Gently
Awake Bouchon
With You Where
Now Future
On the Selephone
More
Awakening Bouchon
Endless Dreams
Dance On
Oh Oh Oh Oh
Now Pirari Pirari
The Selefon
Oh Oh Oh Oh
WooWoo
Can you love?
Can you live?
Dance You
Then be quiet
Do you love me?
Do you love me
No one can stop you from being young.
Please Please Please Please Please Go
Don't Stop I'll go Everybody
Don't Stop I'll go home without a word
Please Please Please Please Go Don't Stop Everybody Don't Stop
Don't Stop No matter how old you get
Crying, being held, blinking
Please Please Please Go
Don't be selfish, please give me love
Get the Enchant Holy Day
Cheerful Summer Feeling
Yay! Super Dog Sun!
Love in a groove
Yes, it's so big
Gather up your courage
Yes More surprises
I want to support my new self
I want to fall in love with a groove
Yes
Romantic Love
Room for you and meRoom for you and me
It's a different view now
Yeah Yeah Yeah
Romantic Love Blossoms
Singing more
As if it's not happening, love is about to begin
I want to do Nagashi Somen on my next day off. What do you want to do?
Morning Musume。 23's Rio Kitagawa and Kanami Ishiguri of Ochanoma present "Halo! Ste. 23 and Kanami Ishiguri of Ochanoma.
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Okay, let's go.
Mr. Ishiguri, who is a certified tea advisor, what kind of tea do you recommend for this season?
It's a tea made with chestnuts in the fall.
This year, Ochanoma is performing at a faster pace than last year!
What have you learned from your many appearances?
How to use time.
What do you want to improve your skills?
The power of being caught on camera.
What do you recommend about your hometown, Hokkaido?
The air is delicious and energizing, so please come!
Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
Which song has had the greatest influence on you today?
Brainstorming by Morning Musume。 Project's brainstorming session.
Oh!
Thank you.
What is the qualification of a tea advisor?
Tea advisor means that I have loved tea since I was a little girl.
I took this picture because I wanted to deepen my love for tea.I took this picture to deepen that love.
Like where the tea comes from.
I wanted to take a picture to deepen my love of tea, like where it comes from.
I want to learn about the good things that tea can do for your body.
It's a certification that allows you to learn about such things.
What do you recommend now?
Chestnut tea?
Yes, I recommend the autumn tea using chestnuts.
I didn't know there was such a thing.
I am very happy to know about it!
I'd also like to hear a little bit more about your hometown, Hokkaido.
I'd like to hear more about Hokkaido, where you're from.
Yes, Hokkaido, really.
The first thing I think about Hokkaido is
I think the first thing people think about Hokkaido is that the air is delicious.
It's really delicious.
I feel like I can do whatever I want in Hokkaido.
It's wonderful!
It is a land of courage and hope.
I hope you all come to Hokkaido.
I've never been to Hokkaido before, so I'd like to go there a lot.
I would like to go there a lot.
Questions for Rio-chan after the VTR
Hello! sta.
me
Tsubaki Factory, if you are only delusional, you're free September 27 on style
Camellia Factory or not September 27 on Style
Harosute.
Next I would like to ask Rio a question from me.I would like to ask Rio a question next.
Yes, please.
Okay, here we go.
Rio-chan was a guest on M-Line Special 2023 last month.
Was there anything impressive about performing with the senior members?
Everyone's power is amazing.
Rio-chan keeps a record of her meals on SNS.
What is your latest favorite dish?
Curry.
If you were to give a catchphrase to the current 14-member Morning Musume。 23, what would your catchphrase be?
Nigiri.
Tell us about your specialties in makeup.
My eyelashes and the use of double liner.
Which song from Hello! Project's history resonates most with your 19-year-old self?
It's "Eien de Ganbatte no Yoroshiku" by S/mileage.
Yes, thank you.
I would like to ask you a question about something that caught my attention,
What is your record of your meals on social networking sites,
I often look at your Instagram and Rio-chan's. I myself love to eat,
I myself love to eat,
You mentioned curry,
What kind of curry do you like?
I like curry, ramen, and cafes,
I've been exploring a lot of ramen and cafes, but I haven't explored curry at all,
I have been exploring many ramen, cafes, etc., but I realized that I have not explored curry at all,
The other day, I went to a famous restaurant in Shimokitazawa,
There was a place where I went to eat vegetable curry for the first time,
I went there for the first time to try vegetable curry, and it was really delicious,
But there are many kinds of curry,
But there are many kinds of curry, and among them, there are those that are a little too crunchy,I'd like to try some of those curries that are a little bit shabby,
And then there are curries that are quite thick,
There are many kinds of curries,
I realized that there are many types of curry that I have never tasted before,
I would like to explore more curry dishes in the future.
That's great.
Next, I would like to ask the current 14-member Morning Musume。 23, if you were to give a catchphrase to the current 14-member Morning Musume,
You mentioned "Niji,
I think we are a group with strong individuality,
We have a wide range of age groups,
We have a wide range of age groups, from 9th term members to 17th term members.
There are so many different types of people in the group,
I think it's really easy to find a lot of individuality in each member, or to like a particular member, or to like a particular part of a member,
I think it is really easy to find a lot of people,
The secondary hand is generally vivid and clear,
I thought it was a perfect fit.
Hallo! The next part will be continued.
Hallo! stay!
Next is the presentation of lyrics that touched my heart.
Yes, so, first of all, do you have any lyrics that touched your heart?
Yes, I, Shiguri, was moved by the song "Kame ni nare" by Kobushi Factory.
This is a song that Ochanoma covered during the spring tour.
I especially love the lyrics of the chorus, "Don't be in a hurry, don't be rotten, don't complain, don't stop, don't stop, don't stop.
The lyrics "Be the turtle that can laugh at the end" are my favorite.
I was a trainee for a long time, and these lyrics saved my life many times.
I love it very much.
I love the lyrics of Sexy Cat's speech.
I love the lyrics of the speech of the sex cat, "You're just busy being inefficient, and you feel like you've done your best without getting any results.
The lyrics are quite harsh, which you can't imagine from the title.
But I really feel that the lyrics are very true.But I really think that's exactly how it is.
I'm the type of person who does things in a hurry at the last minute.
I understand.
I always say that I'm too busy, too busy.
But my colleague Mei Yamazaki is the type of girl who starts preparing for the event a month or so in advance.
That's why, when it comes to this same time of the year...
There's just too much difference in the way we have our hearts and minds set at the same time.
I felt that I shouldn't say "I'm busy, I'm busy, I'm busy" when I'm really just doing it inefficiently.
Oh...
I've always thought that people who can afford to be busy do things in a certain way.
This lyric reminds me to keep that in mind and do my best from now on.
Now, please watch the VTR.
Here you go!
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!
In this corner, we will present the lyrics from the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Kasai, will be presenting.
Here it is.
Ta-da!
This wound is for blooming flowers in the next season.
It's a song about not crying and not making a mistake,
I've been singing this lyric for a long time,
Oh, you are singing it?
Yes, that's right. I sing this part,
I was singing this part when I received the song for the first time,
The song itself is about love,
I thought the lyrics were also applicable to me who was not in love,
I'm the type of person who makes a lot of mistakes and gets hurt a lot.
I'm the type of person who gets depressed, and I get depressed a lot,
It's like I'm not afraid of failure,It's like they don't fear failure in any great way,
It's not about being afraid of failure,
It sounds as if the lyrics are about not being afraid of failure, but rather that the failure was necessary in order to make the best use of it the next time,
Since I became aware of that,
Since I became aware of that, I don't get too depressed when I fail,
I wanted to be a strong woman who doesn't get too depressed about her failures,
I was really encouraged,
I was encouraged by the lyrics, and there was a link between the lyrics and myself,
So I chose this song.
The lyrics are good, aren't they?
I understand it very well.
I think it's a great lyric about taking your failures and using them as food for your own strength,
I think it's a great lyric about how we can take our failures and use them as our strength to move on to the next stage.
I also really like this song,
There are lyrics in this song that I also like, and I think they are stylish,
I like the lyric, "I'd rather wear burgundy rouge than pink lips,
It's in the second verse.
It's in the second verse,
I thought that phrase was very stylish,
It's true.
I thought the lyrics expressed the growth from a child to an adult,
You know, it's stylish, isn't it?
A stylish song.
It's nice.
The way the lyrics are phrased is also very stylish,
I would like you all to listen to it again.
Please look forward to the next episode.
Bye bye.Bye bye.
Morning Musume。' 23's Rio Kitagawa and
Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume'23 and Kanami Ishigiri of Ochanoma will be presenting "Halo! STE, presented by Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。
Morning Musume。 23 started last weekend.
Ochanoma will start their fall tour on October 7.
I have written my resolutions for the fall tour in my sketchbook, and I would like to express them here.
Let me start with me, Rio Kitagawa.
I am also a growth.
As I mentioned earlier, this is the first tour for the 17th term and the last tour for Ms. Fukumura,
I think this is a place where the 17th term members can grow a lot,
I also think that Rio Sakurai, a member of the 16th term, who is participating in the tour as a senior for the first time, will also grow a lot,
I am sure that Rio Sakurai, a 16th term member who will be joining the tour as a senior for the first time, will also grow up a lot,
I think I can learn a lot from them and also from Ms. Fukumura, who will be joining us for the last time,
I would like to do my best so that I can grow up as well.
Next, here is Kanon Ishiguri's resolution.
I am going to conquer the whole country.
As I mentioned earlier, Ochanoma's fall tour will take us to all 47 prefectures of Japan,
As I mentioned earlier, our fall tour is a live house tour that will take us to all 47 prefectures of Japan,
This is a tour where Ochanoma will visit you all over Japan,
We will do our best to deliver Ochanoma to everyone's Ochanoma,
I will do my best to bring Ochanoma to all of you and to conquer the whole country.
That's so wonderful.
Thank you very much.
We have talked with each other about a lot of things,
Are there any other things you are personally looking forward to?
I am.
I am looking forward to seeing the souvenirs from each of the 47 prefectures we will visit,
I am usually not the type to buy many souvenirs when I go on an expedition,
I am not the type of person who usually buys souvenirs when I go on an expedition, but this time I am determined to buy 47 pieces of souvenirs,
I'm going to enjoy myself so much.I am going to enjoy it all.
It is also Mr. Fukumura's last tour,
I want to make a lot of memories of the two of us,
When I get busy with performances, I tend not to have time to take pictures,
But I really want to make time to take lots of pictures, even if I have to force myself to do so,
For example, we may have eaten a delicious meal together, or talked a lot backstage together,
I would like to make a lot of memories, even if they are small ones.
Morning Musume。 23 and Ocha-no-Mama fall tour,
We will really do our best in various places around the country, so please come and visit us.
[Applause]
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the gymnasium of the Yoyogi National Institute of
Hello, everyone gathered in the gymnasium!
Hello!
Now, in 1998, initially called Hello! Hello Project was born in 1998 under the name Hello!
With the support of everyone involved and our fans, we are now celebrating our 25th anniversary,
I would like to thank everyone involved and all of our fans for their support in helping us reach our 25th anniversary.
Thank you very much.
We would like to express our love and gratitude for the past 25 years.
We will be performing live by the OGs and collaborating with the current members,
Please enjoy the live performance by the OGs and the collaboration with the current members of Halo Pro.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Jumping Angel Heart
This summer, I want to be honest with my body.
I'm melting in this heart.
I want you to hold me tenderly
I want to make this a luxurious summer
Sake and CiscobooSake and Ciscoboo
How many times did you laugh?
How many kisses?
How many times have we been jealous?
How many times have we fought too many battles together?
You must have thought
On your chest
I love you I'll wait for you
I'm going to Minimoney!
You know what? I knew it.
Give him salt. I won't give him salt.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors.
Give him salt, give him red.
Osaka-bencho, Yinjinjin!
Jankenpon, jankenpon, jankenpon, jankenpon.
Jankenpon, jankenpon, jankenpon, jankenpon, jankenpon.
Pappappappa, let's dance Shower goal
Pappappappa, pappappa, pappappa, pappappa, pappappa, pappappa, pappappa
Let's sing "Pappa-pappa" Shower goals
Pappa-pappa, it's a good day
Believe in yourself and go
Happiness, safe jacket
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Right, my lady
Baby, my lady
Come on, yo, to the 21, break it down
Down like this
Revolution
All together now
So tonight the nightSo tonight the night
Into the new century Morning
Daughter Drop it
Super, super, super good
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
This earth is beautiful
The earth where we were together
All together now
Yeah!
We fell in love
Uh baby
I fell in love
I've seen the earth
Because of love
Uh baby
Revolution 21
All together now
Love Revolution with Everyone
Revolution 21
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wowWow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow.
HELL Foot WAP Mai Tsukasa Ick Sayonara
I know you're doing your best.
Morning Musume。 23's Rio Kitagawa and Kanami Ishiguri of Ocha no Ma present "Halo! STE, presented by Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。
It's time to say goodbye!
Here is an announcement.
Morning Musume。 Best Selection THE 25th Anniversary is now on sale!
It's a work that really contains 25 years of history, and
We're also going to try to do some of the old units with the current members, and also re-record some of the old songs as 2,3 versions.
We also re-recorded a couple of versions of old songs.
Please listen to it. Please listen to it.
And Morning Musume。 23 is starting its fall tour!
This is the first tour for Nanaki Sincerity and the last tour for Ms. Fukumura.
This is also a setlist that is really filled with 25 years of history.
There are many old and new songs in the setlist.
There really is a lot to see, so please come and visit us if you are in the area!
Yes, Ochanoma will start its fall tour on October 7!
We will tour in 47 prefectures and try our best to grow a lot through this fall tour!
Morning Musume。 23 will perform at Inazuma Rockfest 2023 on October 9!
Unfortunately, we were not able to perform at the festival last year due to an extraction, so this will be our first time performing at the festival.
We are all very excited to be performing for the first time!
We are looking forward to it. Please come and play with us!
The Okayama Bizenji x Ochanoma Community Revitalization Concert will be held on November 19!
Yes, this concert will be accompanied by a bus tour, so
I hope to make many wonderful memories with you all!
Hello! Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel!
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
I'll be with Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。 23's Rio Kitagawa andThe partner is Morning Musume。' 23's Rio Kitagawa and
and Kanami Ishiguri of Ochanoma.
Farewell.